Good boss
老板好
You go first. I'll go to the bathroom
你先回吧我去个卫生间
Good
好
What's wrong with defaulting again
怎么了又要赖账
This is a company
这可是公司哎
What's the matter
怎么了
What if you stop making trouble and let people see you
别闹让人看见怎么办
Unless ah
除非啊
Just give me a kiss
亲我一下就行
What would you like to eat tonight
晚上想吃什么
I'm having dinner with the company tonight
我晚上要跟公司一起聚餐
Mr. Xu invited us all to dinner today
今天徐总请我们大家吃饭
Eat and drink well, everyone
大家吃好喝好
Thank you, boss
谢谢老板
Wish
祝
Our Wonderland culture projects are smooth and profitable
咱们奇境文化的项目都顺顺利利
Smooth and smooth profits
顺顺利利
Cheers, cheers
干杯干杯
Who is Xu Jinfeng
徐津枫是哪位
The brown sugar water you ordered has arrived
你点的红糖水外卖到了
Ah
啊
Not bad
还不错呀
Supplementary recording of Yulu's lines: A total of the above nine schemes were shortlisted for our final selection
玉露台词补录：一共有以上九种方案入围了我们的终选
That's all
以上就是全部内容
What about the current design scheme
现在的设计方案呢
I don't think it can fully meet the needs of customers
我觉得还不能完全满足客户的需求
It is necessary to disassemble the customer's needs in more detail
要把客户的需求拆解的再详细一些
The re-landing plan needs to be changed again
再落地 方案呢还需要再改一改
Let's meet again next week. Let's break up
下周再开会吧 散了吧
What about me? I just spoke as the boss of the company
我呢刚才是作为公司老总的发言
Now it's speaking as a boyfriend
现在是作为男朋友的发言
Then I want an encouragement of love
那我想要一个爱的鼓励
Adong's lines are supplemented: Xu Zong
阿东台词补录：徐总
Someone
某人啊
Last time, knowing that I was a cleanliness freak, I made such a bad move
上次明知我有洁癖还出那么损的招
It's a pity. It's a pity
可惜啊可惜
If you can't hurt the enemy, you can't hurt yourself several times
伤敌不成自损几番
Who knew you had so many stinky problems
谁知道你臭毛病那么多
I'm sorry. I didn't mean that
抱歉啊我不是说那个
It's okay. I'm used to it.
没事我都习惯了而已
It's all subconscious behavior
都是下意识的行为
After which car accident did your parents
那 哪次车祸之后你父母
They all went far away
都去了很远的地方
I'm sorry
对不起啊
I will accompany you in the future
以后我会陪着你的
How are you gonna stay with me
你要怎么陪我
How would you like to be with me
你想怎么陪
I can accompany you as much as I want
我想怎么陪就怎么陪
Feed mom
喂 妈
Ball ball
球球
Okay, I know
好我知道
I thought you said
你不是说
Yeah
是啊
They all moved to America after the car accident
就从出车祸之后他们就都搬去了美国
Isn't this far
这难道不远吗
Okay, my mom just called and said
好了我妈刚才打电话说呢
A friend is going back to China next week
有一个朋友下周要回国了
Let me give you a good treat
让我好好招待一下
Girls
女生
Clever
聪明的呀
Let me show you the photos
让你看看照片
You see
你看
She was a fat boy when she was a child
她小时候啊就是一个胖小子
We all call her Ball Ball
我们都叫她球球
What about next week? Let's have dinner together
下周呢一起吃个饭吧
Let me introduce you to each other
介绍你们认识一下
I don't want it
我不要
Ah Feng
阿枫
It's me, Ball Ball
是我呀球球